RESUME

Name : Manoj Bellamkonda

Qualification: B Tech (Electrical and Electronics Engineering)

Email id : manoj523arjun@gmail.com

Mobile No : (+91) 8892 57 3167

Address : #303, Sri Shiva Sai enclave, CKB Layout Marathahalli, Bangalore-560037

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

8+ years of overall Industry experience in providing User Interface development with most usable enterprise wide applications. Specialized in full static **website development**, **Frontend Development**, 6+ **years** of relevant experience in **React is and Redux**.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Currently working as an **Senior Software Developer** in Xactly corporation, Bangalore from March 2020 to till date.
- Working experience as an **Interactive Developer** in Sapient Consulting, Bangalore from February 2018 to Feb 2020..
- Working experience as a **Software Developer** in Synnov software LLP, Bangalore from October 2015 to January 2018.
- Working experience as **Software Developer** in Quietgrowth Pty Ltd, Bangalore from December 2014 to October 2015.
- Working experience as Web Developer in Pixsello, Bangalore from November 2013 to December

EDUCATION QUALIFICATION

- Bachelor of Technology in Electrical and Electronics Engineering in April 2013 from Vemu Institute of Technology (Affiliated to JNTU, Anantapur), P Kothakota with 72.16%.
- Intermediate (MPC) in March 2009 from Govt Jr College, Nandavanam with 87.4%.
- SSC in March 2007 from ZPH School, Mogarala with 87.16%.

SKILLS

Web Technologies : HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3

Scripting Languages : JavaScript, jQuery, React Js, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Webpack, TypeScript

Basics, Backbone Js and Web Accessibility

CSS Frameworks : Bootstrap

Script Editors : Sublime text 3 Editor, Visual Studio

Testing Frameworks: Jest, Enzyme, React Testing Library

Graphics Tools : Photoshop CS6

PROJECTS WORKED ON

Xactly Corporation

Project 1:

Project name: Xactly Corporation own product (Incent)

Responsibilities:

- Currently contributing to the initial setup of new module if Incent Product which is Home End User Dashboard by sing React 17, Webpack 5, Redux toolkit.
- Work with the creative team and create React Components. Currently leading the Incent Re-skin project and working on creating the common functionalities for this project using React, jQuery, Bootstrap.
- I was contributed to the Xactly Design System Prism components node module private package. I created New components like XCheckBox, XSlidePanel, XTreelist
- I was one of the code member in implementation MCL feature of Incent product
- Implemented the form validations, modals, accordions and Tabs using jQuery and JavaScript.

Sapient Consulting

Project 1:

Project name: CF-AC-2019 Init

Client: Fiat Chrysler Automobiles N.V

Duration: on-going project

Responsibilities:

- Work with the creative team and create the re-usable components using react.
- Implemented Accessibility for the web application as per the WACG standards.
- Using Jest framework for react component unit testing.

Project 2:

Project name: GLS | Portfolio 1

Client: Goldman Sachs

Duration: 9 months

Responsibilities:

- Work with the creative team and create the page using the react components.
- Used redux library as state management for the web application.
- Used Redux Saga as middleware for web API calls.
- Used Jest and Enzyme as testing frameworks for unit testing. We have covered 90% of the code coverage as a part of unit testing.
- Used redux form module for forms creation and forms validations.

Synnov Software LLP

Project 1:

Project name: homestudio.com

Client: Home Studio

Duration: 2 years

Responsibilities:

- Work with the creative team and create the responsive browser compatibility web pages using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Implemented the form validations, modals, accordions and Tabs using jQuery and JavaScript.

Quietgrowth

Project 1:

Project name: quietgrowth.com.au

Duration: 11 months

Responsibilities:

-	Work with the creative team and create the responsive browser compatibility
	web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

•	Implemented the form validations	, modals,	accordions	and Tabs	using j	Query
	and JavaScript.					

hereby assure you that all particulars give above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief				
Place:				
Date:	(MANOJ BELLAMKONDA)			